(Leonard:)and see the look
on Sheldon's stupid face
(Leonard:)when he sees that I didn't
let this get to me.
(Penny:)Sheldon's not here.
Why don't you take the sweater off?
-There's a principle at stake!
-Which is?
(Lucy:)Oh, I don't know.
Who cares? Look at me!
(Penny:)Oh, my God!
Is that sweater made of bees?
(Penny:)Come on, take it off. I won't tell.
(Leonard:)No, no, honey, if I take it off,
Sheldon wins.
(Penny:)Sweetie, every night you don't
kill him in his sleep, he wins.
No, it's almost done.
(Leonard:)I just... I have to find
the next of kin, and send 'em the DVD
(Leonard:)and then just wait for someone
with my complexion to die
(Leonard:)so I can get a skin graft.
(Penny:)Smile.
(Leonard:)What is that? What is that for?
(Penny:)So you can send it to Princeton
and get your money back.
(Amy:)I must say, Sheldon,
you're handling this DVD business
(Amy:)with an impressive amount
of maturity.
(Sheldon:)I don't know why that surprises you.
I'm a grown man.